<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>The XXXth. of January. Or, An anniversary. Being a poeme dedicated to the Qveene of Great Brittain, at the Lovre: January the 30.th/20.th.</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1652</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 12 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 9 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2012-10">2012-10 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">B01935</idno>
            <idno type="STC">Wing C125</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC R170337</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">52211719</idno>
            <idno type="OCLC">ocm 52211719</idno>
            <idno type="VID">175451</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. B01935)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 175451)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English Books, 1641-1700 ; 2737:11)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>The XXXth. of January. Or, An anniversary. Being a poeme dedicated to the Qveene of Great Brittain, at the Lovre: January the 30.th/20.th.</title>
                  <author>S. C.</author>
                  <author>Henrietta Maria, Queen, consort of Charles I, King of England, 1609-1669.</author>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>10 p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>[s.n.],</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>Printed in Paris :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1652.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>Dedication: To the royal majestie of Henrietta Maria, Queene of Great Brittain, France, and Ireland, &amp;c. Signed: S.C.</note>
                  <note>Imperfect: print show-through with slight loss of text.</note>
                  <note>Reproduction of the original in the University of Texas, Austin Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>Charles --  I, --  King of England, 1600-1649 --  Poetry.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2008-09</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2008-10</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2011-07</date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2011-07</date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2012-05</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:175451:1"/>
            <pb facs="tcp:175451:1"/>
            <p>THE XXX<hi rend="sup">th</hi>. OF JANUARY. OR, AN ANNIVERSARY.</p>
            <p>BEING A POEME DEDICATED TO THE QVEENE OF GREAT BRITTAIN, AT THE LOVRE: January the
<list>
                  <item>30.th</item>
                  <item>20.th</item>
               </list>
            </p>
            <p>Printed at PARIS. M.D.C.LII.</p>
         </div>
         <div type="dedication">
            <pb facs="tcp:175451:2"/>
            <pb facs="tcp:175451:2"/>
            <head>TO THE ROYALL MAJESTIE OF HENRIETTA MARIA Queene of great <hi>Brittain, France,</hi> and <hi>Jreland, &amp;c.</hi>
            </head>
            <opener>
               <salute>MADAM,</salute>
            </opener>
            <p>
               <seg rend="decorInit">J</seg>T is now high time that your Prince<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly Eyes ſhould no longer contract redneſs from teares but a brave fire from Revenge, That you ſhould deal with your Paſſion as the generous <hi>ORMOND</hi> with that infamous fire-brand of the world that Canker to the Royall Stock and Branches <hi>CROMWELL,</hi> ſuffer it to poſſeſse ſome Out<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>skirts and frontiers of your Soule, that by the expanſion of his incroachments its Spirits may be waſted and layd open for Ruine; And your victorious Reaſon (contracting all its forces)
<pb n="2" facs="tcp:175451:3"/> ſweep all ſuch treacherous Invaders from the face of the world, and leave nothing of it in Nature but a Memory, which may make it ſti<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>k<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap> to all Poſterity.</p>
            <p>
               <hi>
                  <gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>o<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>cia</hi>'s Coales are of no further uſe for d<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>ſpai<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>e, all they can bee ſerviceable in, is to create a flame to which the barbarous Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bels must be fuell, and the fire may bee a Purifier to the Region of Soveraignty, clee<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ring all the Ayre from thoſe two greatest Plagues to Order and Mankind <hi>Rebellion</hi> and <hi>Rigicide.</hi> God has now ripened them for the Sickle of Revenge; it is highly oppor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tune to ſhake them from the trees of Autho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rity and Rapine whereon they hang, and ſince hanging is naturall for ſuch <hi>Gomorrah</hi> Ap<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ples, <hi>Tyburne</hi> in England is the properest place in the world for ſuch <hi>fruits,</hi> if their rottenneſſe bee not too violent Eye-ſores to the view, and of too great a Stench to the Noſe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thrils of Paſſengers.</p>
            <pb n="3" facs="tcp:175451:3"/>
            <p>The <hi>30.<hi rend="sup">th</hi>
               </hi> of <hi>January</hi> ſhall bee recko<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ned amongst thoſe Ominous dayes which are fatall to the repoſe and ſafetie of Nati<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ons, which though it antecede heere that in <hi>ENGLAND</hi> by tenne dayes, yet my paſſi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>on of Revenge, and my engagement to fol<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>low that Standard of your Heroick Sonne, which muſt carry with it a Reſtitution of the World to Lawes, Libertie, Religion, Conſcience, and all Obligations divine and Humane, hath made mee make uſe of the Kalender in <hi>FRANCE,</hi> and preſent an <hi>An<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>niverſary</hi> upon the most horrid Murther the Sunne ever view'd; not to ſtirre up your un-exampled Pietie to Teares, but to awake your owne Royall and all other Loyall Bo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſomes to revenge; which, when it ſhall breake foorth in its just magnitude and demenſions, the Rebells will confeſſe, that Our long Silence is like a Calme, whoſe
<pb n="4" facs="tcp:175451:4"/> unſuſpected tranquillity is followed by nothing leſse dangerous then totally ſubverting Earth<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>quakes, or univerſally conſuming Thun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ders.</p>
            <p>
               <hi>MADAME.</hi>
               <lb/> The <hi>Perſian</hi> Princes had a conſtant Monitor to remember them of <hi>Greeke</hi> affronts and injuries, may this <hi>Anniverſary</hi> bee your Remembrancer that all <hi>Europe</hi> is engaged to your aſſiſtance; that you have a fate more no<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ble impending then to live in exile, or un re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>venged; that you have a Sonne, who, by his fiery perſecutions and Vertues, will, one day, make good in his examples, all which is ever related of the most excellent Princes; That there is a Nation which with infinite groanes implores its reſtitution to Monarchy, its re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>demption from Rebellion, in which it is fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tally captivated and engulphed, and (which, <hi>MADAME,</hi> deſerves a Lower ranke amongst thoſe more Majeſtique concernments) let it
<pb n="5" facs="tcp:175451:4"/> bee a ſpeaking teſtimony to the World, that J am (in Spight of all Revolutions occaſioned by Thieves, Rebells, and Regicid<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>s.)</p>
            <closer>
               <signed>Your MAJESTIES, and all your Royall Fami<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>i<gap reason="illegible" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap> Most humble, and never changeable Servant Subject, <hi>S. C.</hi>
               </signed>
            </closer>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="poem">
            <pb facs="tcp:175451:5"/>
            <pb n="7" facs="tcp:175451:5"/>
            <head>ALLEGIANCE TO THE MEMORY OF OUR LATE MURTHERED SOVERAIGNE CHARLES THE I.</head>
            <lg>
               <l>SUch was the Pride of Murther in our loſs,</l>
               <l>To dubbe the Scaffold equall to the Croſs.</l>
               <l>Since the world's <hi>Crucifixe;</hi> all butcheries</l>
               <l>The <hi>Jury</hi> finds Chance-Medley, unto this.</l>
               <l>The Primitive and Modern <hi>Martyrs</hi> all,</l>
               <l>Members of CHARLES his Body Myſticall.</l>
               <l>The univerſall <hi>Bill</hi> of Martyrdome,</l>
               <l>In him, contracted to a <hi>Totall Summe.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>'Tis thought thy Saviour, only <hi>Priest,</hi> would dye,</l>
               <l>And leave his Kingly ſufferings to <hi>thee.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>In Life and Death his <hi>Vice-roy,</hi> as if all</l>
               <l>His Offices were <hi>Hypoſtaticall.</hi>
               </l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>How durſt they think hee mortall was, or ſay</l>
               <l>He leſſe then <hi>Angels,</hi> were aſſumed Clay?</l>
               <l>Fool'd Tyrant Wretches who believe him dead,</l>
               <l>Who from <hi>Humanitie</hi> but vaniſhed.</l>
               <l>
                  <hi>Faith</hi> being weake, a <hi>Demonſtration</hi>'s He,</l>
               <l>To looſe the Riddle of <hi>Theanthrophie.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>To all Religious underſtanding Eyes,</l>
               <l>
                  <hi>Humanitie</hi> was but his Late diſguiſe.</l>
               <pb n="8" facs="tcp:175451:6"/>
               <l>But ſo much <hi>Deity</hi> may juſtly grudge,</l>
               <l>To be condem'd, and <hi>Barrabas</hi> his Iudge.</l>
               <l>When every drop of Bloud hee ſhed, was much</l>
               <l>Too precious, to redeem the <hi>Soules</hi> of ſuch.</l>
               <l>For had old ADAM ſpawn'd no better <hi>ſeed,</hi>
               </l>
               <l>Th' Eternall <hi>Sonne</hi> had never liv'd or dyed.</l>
               <l>If his Poſterity had all been ſuch,</l>
               <l>The bloud of Buls and Goates had been too much.</l>
               <l>Lord, was it not enough, thy ſelfe to dye,</l>
               <l>But thou muſt ſuffer too by <hi>Deputie?</hi>
               </l>
               <l>Who his pure Breath a prey to Villaines gave,</l>
               <l>Not worthy to be <hi>Sextons</hi> to his Grave.</l>
               <l>Shov'ling his <hi>Monarchy,</hi> as if it muſt</l>
               <l>Follow like <hi>Earth</hi> to <hi>Earth,</hi> and Duſt to duſt.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>How will the <hi>Hoogen</hi> Chandlers ſcorn our fate,</l>
               <l>When HEWSON vampes and underlayes the State?</l>
               <l>When PRIDE in <hi>Ale,</hi> and Dray-man <hi>Buffe</hi> ſhal ſing</l>
               <l>I've ſlaine <hi>Goliah</hi> with a <hi>Small-Beere</hi> Sling.</l>
               <l>And drawne out Royaltie ſo neere the <hi>Lee,</hi>
               </l>
               <l>This Hand muſt tappe a well hopp'd <hi>Anarchie.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>Their Babby-<hi>Generall</hi> is a fine thing,</l>
               <l>Such I have ſeene, in Childrens feaſtings, <hi>King.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>Whoſe bloudy Treaſons onely him engage</l>
               <l>As <hi>Obligation</hi> ſealed under age.</l>
               <l>Now all's diſpatch'd; were hee demanded why</l>
               <l>He muſt ſend Poſt to CROMVVELL for a Lye.</l>
               <l>'Tis time to paſſe from this infernall hoſt,</l>
               <l>From whom I riſe as from the Nethermoſt:</l>
               <pb n="9" facs="tcp:175451:6"/>
               <l>And paſſe, as through a <hi>Purgatorie</hi> flame,</l>
               <l>To a prepared Bliſſe in CHARLES his Name.</l>
               <l>Whil'ſt I with trembling and Religious care,</l>
               <l>Doe goe unto my mourning, as my <hi>Pray'r.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>I doe repent, I have prophan'd his Herſe,</l>
               <l>And Sacred Aſhes, with un-hallow'd Verſe.</l>
               <l>To whom, as one Religious Votarie,</l>
               <l>Three Pilgrim Kingdomes owe their Pietie.</l>
               <l>Though <hi>Saint's</hi> too mean a Name for him, wee know</l>
               <l>His Vertues Canoniz'd him below:</l>
               <l>In Navigation, as the <hi>Mariner</hi>
               </l>
               <l>Steer's not by th' <hi>Pole,</hi> but by the neereſt <hi>Starre.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>So that devotion erres not from the <hi>Text</hi>
               </l>
               <l>Which hee inſpires, whoſe Vertue was the next;</l>
               <l>So farre the ſame, they differ not at all,</l>
               <l>But as the Copie from th' <hi>Originall.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>GOD did to him ſo much his Likeneſſe deal,</l>
               <l>'T might ſeem his ſecond Precept to repeal.</l>
               <l>Whoſe indiſputable Divinity,</l>
               <l>None (but this <hi>Arrian</hi> army) dares deny.</l>
               <l>And now, to view his Conſtellation,</l>
               <l>
                  <hi>Sadduces</hi> yeeld a <hi>Reſurrection.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>So hee all Hereſies ſeemes to confute,</l>
               <l>Which, at his Maſters death, were in diſpute.</l>
               <l>Cloath'd now with Light no Contrary he knowes,</l>
               <l>Except the utter darkneſs of his Foes.</l>
               <l>What Comets ſhould have uſhered his fall,</l>
               <l>Doe waite as Torches at his Funerall.</l>
               <pb n="10" facs="tcp:175451:7"/>
               <l>Hee ſo be-dayes the Night, th' <hi>Aſtrologer</hi>
               </l>
               <l>That GOD hath ſnuff'd the <hi>Firmament</hi> does ſwear.</l>
               <l>He appeares not only Starre to every ſence,</l>
               <l>But Spheare; and hee his owne Intelligence.</l>
               <l>So glorious, that this Riddle he begets,</l>
               <l>
                  <hi>The Sunne then ſolely riſes when hee ſets.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>Whoſe Guid his ſaving light is, ere they reſt</l>
               <l>Shall over-take the Wiſe-men of the <hi>Eaſt.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>Who ſo his wiſdomes juſt Admirer is,</l>
               <l>Sayes <hi>Solomon's</hi> was Typicall to his.</l>
               <l>Had they, and <hi>Shebah's</hi> Queen, liv'd at one time,</l>
               <l>With what deſire would ſhee have Cuckol'd Him!</l>
               <l>Although his Continence was ſo divine,</l>
               <l>He it alone embrac'd as Concubine.</l>
               <l>A <hi>Veſtall</hi> might have layne with Him in Bed,</l>
               <l>And riſe with her Religious Mayden-head.</l>
               <l>How did hee in St. <hi>Michael's</hi> Angell-vein</l>
               <l>Confute thoſe <hi>Devils</hi> which durſt him arraigne!</l>
               <l>If wee the Muſter-roll of <hi>Virtues</hi> call,</l>
               <l>The Name of CHARLES may anſwer for them all.</l>
               <l>As what wee attribute to God muſt be</l>
               <l>It ſelfe, the abſolute Divinitie.</l>
               <l>So <hi>Reaſon</hi> coupled with moralitie,</l>
               <l>This Definition gets that they were hee.</l>
               <l>Who now for eyther ſeekes (hee being ſpent)</l>
               <l>Without a <hi>Subſtance</hi> lookes for <hi>Accident.</hi>
               </l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>But, as the Sunne ſets only unto Us,</l>
               <l>And never ſhines him-ſelfe leſſe glorious,</l>
               <pb n="11" facs="tcp:175451:7"/>
               <l>Our <hi>Sol's</hi> eclipſe was to improve his Light,</l>
               <l>But ſmother us in an Aegyptian Night.</l>
               <l>As Earth-quakes doe deſtroy from Mile to mile,</l>
               <l>And faſt foundations Filip Croſſe and Pile,</l>
               <l>The Center yet being never ſtirr'd at all;</l>
               <l>So wee (not CHARLES) are bruiſed in his Fall.</l>
               <l>His Execution was his Subject's Paine,</l>
               <l>They loſt their <hi>King,</hi> and yet their <hi>King</hi> doth raigne</l>
               <l>Not as a Deaths-head Shell, or a Grave-Stone,</l>
               <l>Memento's are for Mortals of their owne.</l>
               <l>In this ſad Paper every one may ſee,</l>
               <l>His Epitaph, in his owne Elegie.</l>
               <l>Without a Contradiction 't may bee ſaid,</l>
               <l>
                  <hi>Though hee did Dye, not hee, but wee are Dead.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>What dying life is ours, that He muſt dye,</l>
               <l>And wee, that doe ſurvive him, Putrifie?</l>
               <l>But ſtay his Urne is warme; and, at his Name,</l>
               <l>His Aſhes ſtart, and wake into a flame.</l>
               <l>Through all the Shop of ſublunary things,</l>
               <l>Two are immortall, <hi>Phoenixes,</hi> and <hi>Kings.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>Like Angels, each a Species, makes alone,</l>
               <l>Yet neyther dyes without Succeſſion.</l>
               <l>Draw, draw, great Son; and let thy thirſty Steele,</l>
               <l>Their Bowels tappe till thy full vengeance reele.</l>
               <l>Ride like a Whirle-wind driving on the floud,</l>
               <l>That <hi>Thames</hi> may know no full Sea, but of bloud.</l>
               <l>Hee that not followes may he drowne ith' Streame</l>
               <l>Till brave Revenge hath ſwept the Land ſo cleane</l>
               <pb n="10" facs="tcp:175451:8"/>
               <l>That all thy blaſted Enemies wee ſee,</l>
               <l>Like <hi>Sodomes</hi> Apples rot upon the tree.</l>
               <l>And Travellers praiſe thy Executions,</l>
               <l>For Paving Road-wayes with the Rebels Bones.</l>
            </lg>
            <trailer>FIN.</trailer>
            <pb facs="tcp:175451:8"/>
            <pb facs="tcp:175451:9"/>
            <pb facs="tcp:175451:9" rendition="simple:additions"/>
         </div>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
